Guide to the David Westheimer literary papers, 1940-1997 MS 345
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series VII: Addendum
  - Sub-Series I: Works, Houston Post Colums
    - Senior Women Web - "The Bomb..." Blast article and correspondence (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Stalag Luft III Ex-Prisoners of War - 47th Annual Reunion Membership List (Box 35, Folder 20)